http://www.covplus.com/privacy-policy

Rental Reimbursement
Personal Injury Protection (PIP)
Commercial Auto Insurance
Business Owners Policy (BOP)
Home & Auto Insurance
Combining your home and auto policies can benefit you with discounts that help you save and additional coverage options to make your life easier.
Rental Reimbursement
Personal Injury Protection (PIP)
Medical Payments Coverage
Choosing the right auto insurance is the key to keeping you and your car safe on the road in the event of an accident or other vehicle damage.
High Value and High-Risk Homeowners Insurance
Learn more about the home insurance we provide.
Other Personal Insurance
Identity Theft
Personal Umbrella Insurance
Data Backup
Keep your confidential information and personal assets secure with extended coverage options including personal umbrella insurance.
Snowmobile Insurance
Insure your freedom for adventure with a recreational vehicle policy that covers everything from your boat and RV to your ATV or motorcycle.
Additional Insurance Services
Special Event Insurance
Other Services
Wedding Insurance and Special Event Insurance
Take care of all your specialty insurance needs and other services with extended policy options for your convenience and satisfaction.
Veterinary Insurance
Industry-specific risks make it impossible for insurance companies to lump together one insurance plan for every business.
Coverage for Your Business
Commercial General Liability
Workers Compensation
Commercial Auto Insurance
Business Owners Policy (BOP)
Van Insurance
We’re committed to keeping your business protected so you can focus on your day-to-day operations.
Email Us
Call Us Today!
Rental Reimbursement
Personal Injury Protection (PIP)
Commercial Auto Insurance
Business Owners Policy (BOP)
Privacy Policy
We value you as a customer and respect your right to privacy. We know that you purchase our products and services because you trust that we stand behind our promises. We pledge our commitment to treat your information responsibly. We created this privacy policy to show you that we are working hard to protect your privacy.
Information sharing and opt out
We do not sell your personal information to anyone for any reason. We do not share it, except for the reasons described below, which are permitted by federal and state law. Therefore, there is no need for you to opt out. If we change our policy, we will tell you and give you a chance to opt out before we share your information.
Confidentiality and security
We use physical and technical safeguards to protect your information. We restrict access to your information to those who need it to perform their jobs. Third-party business partners are bound by law to use the information only for our purposes. They may not disclose it or use it in any other way. We comply with all data security laws.
Collecting your personal information
We collect personal information about you from different sources. For example, we collect information you send us on applications and forms. We also collect information from your transactions with our sister companies, others, or us. We may collect information from a consumer-reporting agency or a medical provider. This collection depends on the product or service you request.
Disclosing your personal information
We do not sell your information to anyone. We may disclose this information to a business that carries out services and marketing for us. We may disclose your information as required or permitted by law. We may disclose your information for a legal or regulatory purpose. These include the following types of information.
We may disclose information we receive from you on applications or other forms. This may include your name, address, beneficiaries, Social Security number and family member information. This may also include assets, income, and the property address and value.
We may disclose information from your transactions with our sister companies, or us. This may include your account balance, policy coverage, and payment history. This may also include premium paid, preferences, claims, and purchase method.
We may disclose information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency or other report. This may include, your credit report, motor vehicle and driver data. This may also include medical and employment data, loss history reports, and other driver data. This disclosure depends on the products you select.
We may disclose information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. As permitted by law, we may disclose some information to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements.
Using your medical information
We sometimes must collect medical information to provide you a product or to pay a claim. We do not use or share it for any purpose, except the following:
Underwriting insurance
Administering your policy, account, or claim
As required or permitted by law
As otherwise authorized by you
Internet Policies
What information does Coverage Plus Insurance Agency collect from Web sites? Coverage Plus Insurance Agency may collect the information you provide when you:
Request information from the Coverage Plus Insurance Agency Web site
Use online tools and calculators
Apply online for products
Subscribe to online services
Complete an online form
Conduct transactions online
Apply for a job online
Coverage Plus Insurance Agency contracts with certain unaffiliated business partners who help us deliver online products and services. They may keep the information you provide. Other online activities are listed below.
Visitor Data
Coverage Plus Insurance Agency collects site-aggregate and customer-specific information about the pages you view on our site. We log IP addresses, browser and platform types, domain names, access times and referral data. We also collect information a customer volunteers on surveys and electronic forms. This information is used to improve our Web site.
Coverage Plus Insurance Agency gathers data on its Web site. This is a standard industry practice and is used to find out how visitors use our site. We collect aggregate information on the public areas of our Web site. We also collect information on an individual basis on areas of our Web site that require visitors to logon using an ID and password. We may collect the following data:
How many people visit our Web site
The pages they visit and the features they use
How long they stay on our Web site
The Web site people come from before reaching our Web site
Use of "Cookies"
We store a cookie on your computer when you visit our Web site. A cookie is a tiny piece of information that is required to create and maintain a secure session. Cookies let you request information and do business online. Cookies do not have confidential or personal information. They do not track a user after leaving our Web site. We use a third-party tracking utility, which may set cookies, to analyze how users move within our Web site.
Other Online Security
We also use a Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). This keeps all information confidential when it is sent between our Web site and your computer.
E-mail
We keep the e-mail you send to us. If you agree to receive e-mail messages from us, we will keep the information you give us to send e-mail of specific interest to you. If you choose to send us e-mail, we keep your e-mail, your e-mail address, and our reply. Please be careful about the information you give us in e-mail. As with any public Web site, this communication may not be secure.
Web Links
It is important to note that other companies or organizations may have links on the Coverage Plus Insurance Agency family of Web sites. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or security of information by the companies or organizations outside of the Coverage Plus Insurance Agency family of companies. Please read the privacy policy of Web sites reached through the use of links from the Coverage Plus Insurance Agency family of Web sites.
Why does Coverage Plus Insurance Agency collect information on its Web site?
Coverage Plus Insurance Agency or our business partners use the information from our Web sites for many purposes:
Edits and feedback
Marketing and promotions
Analysis of user behavior
Product development
Content improvement
Informing advertisers how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements
Customize Web site content and layout
What happens if Coverage Plus Insurance Agency changes its privacy policy?
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on our homepage. This way you always know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
If we decide to use your personal information in a different way than for the use that we told you when we collected it, we will notify you by posting a note on our Web site for 30 days.
Questions
We value our customers and want you to understand how we use the information we collect. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
We will provide you a copy of your personal information that we control and can reasonably retrieve. To access your information, you must provide the following:
All policy numbers you want to access.
Please sign your request and have your signature notarized. This ensures the identity of the person requesting the information.
We do not currently charge a fee to cover the cost of providing you with a copy of this information. However, we do reserve the right to charge a small fee in the future.
You may request that we correct your personal information in our files. Please note that we do not control information provided by third parties. So, you will need to contact the third party to correct any information from them.
Sometimes we obtain your consumer or credit report. If so, you may request the credit-reporting agency's name and address. You may ask the agency to give you a copy of your report.
Please send any inquiries to us at:
Coverage Plus Insurance Agency
ATTN: Privacy Department
750 E McGlincy Lane, Suite 109
Campbell, CA 95008
When you write to us, please include your name, address, and policy number, and your agent name and number, if you know it. You can contact your agent to change information that we control, such as your address. Or, you may contact your Coverage Plus Insurance Agency customer service representative. The phone number is in your policy packet.
This privacy statement describes our privacy practices for both current and former customers. We will provide one copy of this notice to joint policy or contract holders. Please share this information with everyone covered by your policy or contract. If you request, we will send more copies of this statement.
Thank you for choosing Coverage Plus Insurance Agency. We look forward to building a lifetime relationship with you.
Allied Property and Casualty Insurance Company
AMCO Insurance Company
Depositors Insurance Company
Nationwide Mutual Insurance Company
Nationwide Agribusiness Insurance Company
Colonial County Mutual Insurance Company
Our Location
Coverage Plus Insurance Agency
Testimonials
I have been using the Coverage Plus Insurance Agency, where Chris is the owner and broker. He is very knowledgeable and knows the insurance market well. Chris has always been recommending the best possible product for my situation, finding a great balance maximizing coverage and minimizing cost, without compromising integrity. Chris recommended an insurance company that puts the customer first, provide excellent service at a reasonable price AND is financially viable, which is very important these days. I would definitely recommend Chris and the Coverage Plus Insurance Agency for your insurance needs.
Jesper S
The first time Chris surprised me was when he achieved the unthinkable: obtaining reasonable cover at very affordable prices when I first moved to the US and had virtually no credit and driving history here (apparently, having driven for 25 years+ does not count).
Not content with that, he managed to improve coverage, at lower rates, as soon as was feasible – despite my having previously believed that “affordable coverage” and “Porsche” would never go into the same sentence.
Ever since, I’ve been assisted very promptly whenever I had a query / claim, and he’s definitely succeeded in making me feel like I’m his only client – which I very much trust not to be the case, as I wish him and Coverage Plus every success.
Marco M
After exhausting research and numerous phone calls with auto insurance companies, I was referred to Chris’s services by a friend. I got an email from Chris requesting a few details about myself and the car I needed insurance for, and shortly after replying to it, I received a very well priced quote with full coverage. With a few customizations I was able to get an awesome deal for literally half the price I was paying at the moment, I immediately called my current company and cancelled and switched to the policy Chris suggested. All of this was done over email within a few hours, I truly enjoyed doing business with Chris and definitely recommend anyone looking for a fast and easy way to get the best deals in auto insurance.
Nikhil I
Chris has taken care of all of my insurance needs for many years now. He is extremely knowledgeable and always considers the overall scenario before recommending a policy. My company switched to his recommendations on Corporate policies and we have saved quite a bit in premiums. I have referred Chris to clients many times and the result is consistent, Chris did a great job for us. I can recommend Chris without reservation.
Rick S
Chris works incredibly hard, is always available and consistently responded to me faster than anyone else I contacted. He is knowledgeable and optimizes cost and all factors. I have taken 3 policies from him in one year of knowing him.
Parnian K
I have known Chris Robinson for over ten years. He is a true professional. I would recommend Chris for any business endeavor that requires trust, character and integrity. I consider him a valued member of my business network as well as a dear and valued friend.
Scott M
I have been one of your clients for one year now.
I am writing you to express my appreciation for outstanding customer service Nora has always provided me during this time: Always prompt, courteous and extremely professional.
As I was in corporate sales for over 25 years (Cisco, Google, etc), I appreciate and value the high quality service your organization provides.
I am sure Nora's efficiency is a direct reflection of your leadership, so Congratulations Chris!
You guys can certainly count on me as a loyal and appreciative client.
Campbell, CA,
San Jose, CA,
Los Gatos, CA,
Cupertino, CA,
Sunnyvale, CA,
Saratoga, CA,
and surrounding areas.
Licensed in CA License #0b3442
Privacy | Site Map
